The Company is a romance, music, drama film directed by Robert Altman.
Ensemble drama centered around a group of ballet dancers, with a focus on one
young dancer who's poised to become a principal performer.
Loretta 'Ry' Ryan, played by Neve Campbell.
Alberto Antonelli, played by Malcolm McDowell.
Josh, played by James Franco.
Harriet, played by Barbara E. Robertson.
Edouard, played by William Dick.
Susie, played by Susie Cusack.
The Company is a 2003 American drama film directed by Robert Altman with a screenplay by
Barbara Turner from a story by Turner and star and co-producer Neve Campbell.
The film also stars Malcolm McDowell and James Franco, and
is set in the company of the Joffrey Ballet.
The film explores themes of chicago, illinois, dancer,
ballet dancer, ballet, choreographer.
The tone is emotional.